smartdnsproxy.com 2016-11-04

# Privacy Policy | Smart DNS Proxy

This privacy policy ("Policy") covers the website http://www.smartdnsproxy.com which are owned and operated by Global Stealth, Incorporated ("SmartDNSProxy", "we", "us", "our"), and all associated SmartDNSProxy services (“Services”) provided by Global Stealth, Inc. through these Websites.

####  What we collect

Global Stealth, Inc. may collect personally identifiable information from Users in variety of ways on it's websites, including through online forms for ordering it's services and some other instances Users may get invited to volunteer such information. 

####  How We Use Information

Global Stealth, Inc. collects and uses such information only insofar as is it deems reasonably necessary in order to provide our Services, for us to manage and send you notices regarding your account, and for us to send you notices regarding the Services. We however will NOT share this information with trusted affiliates, independent contractors, business partners or outside entities.

####  How We Secure The Information

We protect all Personal Information with industry standard security systems. We restrict access to Personal Information collected about you to any connection other than Our automation system. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.

####  How We Secure The Information

We do not allow using our service for any kind of illegal actions - carding, spam and hacking. We reserve the right to terminate, without warning, any account that violates this policy. Usage of services constutures acceptance and understanding of this policy.

####  Privacy Policy Changes

We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. We will post those changes to this privacy statement on the home page and other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. This Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any party.

####  Privacy Policy Changes

Users may direct questions concerning this Privacy Policy by email to
